<resources xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools">
    <string name="app_name">Warhammer40K</string>

    <string-array name="damageNum">
        <item>1</item>
        <item>2</item>
        <item>3</item>
        <item>4</item>
        <item>5</item>
        <item>1d3</item>
        <item>1d6</item>
        <item>2d3</item>
        <item>2d6</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="damageModNum">
        <item>-1</item>
        <item>0</item>
        <item>1</item>
        <item>2</item>
        <item>3</item>
        <item>4</item>
        <item>5</item>

    </string-array>

    <string-array name="definitions">
        <item>Attack</item>
        <item>Armor Saving Throw</item>
        <item>Armor Penetration (AP)</item>
        <item>Damage Roll</item>
        <item>Feel No Pain</item>
        <item>Hits</item>
        <item>Invulnerable Saving Throw</item>
        <item>Random Damage</item>
        <item>Skill</item>
        <item>Strength</item>
        <item>Toughness</item>
        <item>Wounds</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name= "wounding">
        "Strength: How powerful unit attacks are \n \n"
        "Toughness: A model's durability \n \n"
        "Wounds: Successful hits that the enemy must make their armor/invulnerable saves against \n \n"
        "Damage Roll: The roll that determines the amount of damage caused to a target \n \n"
        "Random Damage: A random damage modifier selected after a d3/d6 dice roll"</string>
    <string name="hitting">
        "Attacks/Shots: Attacks are ranged or melee depending on weapon type used \n \n"
        "Unit Weapon Skill: A skill on the datasheet listed under WS or BS heading. This represents the minimum result required to successfully hit a target with a weapon. "
                           </string>
    <string name="saves">
        "Armor Save: An armor saving throw is a saving throw made using a models save characteristic " \n \n
        "AP (Armor Penetration): A weapons ability to penetrate the armor of the target, expressed on the units data sheet as “AP” in the weapons stat line" \n \n
        "Invulnerable Save: A saving throw that can not be modified by anything other than niche special rules, examples include saves granted by storm shields, Iron halos or refactor shields" \n \n
        "Feel No Pain: A saving throw rolled after armor saves are taken but before damage is finalized, examples include an Apothecaries aura ability"</string>
    <string name="attack">Attack: An attack is either a ranged attack or melee attack depending on the weapon type used to make the attack</string>
    <string name="armorsavingthrow">Armor Saving Throw: An armor saving throw is a saving throw made using a models save characteristic</string>
    <string name="ap">Armor Penetration (AP): A weapons ability to penetrate the armor of the target, expressed on the units data sheet as “AP” in the weapons stat line</string>
    <string name="damageroll">Damage Roll: The roll made to determine the amount of damage caused to a target</string>
    <string name="feelnopain">Feel No Pain: A saving throw rolled after armor saves are taken but before damage is finalized, examples include an Apothecaries aura ability</string>
    <string name="hits">Hits: The successful number of attacks</string>
    <string name="invulnerable">Invulnerable Saving Throw: A saving throw that can not be modified by anything other than niche special rules, examples include saves granted by storm shields, Iron halos or refactor shields</string>
    <string name="randomdamage">Random Damage: some weapons use a d3 or d6 for their damage, making the result random. Common examples are melta weapons 1d6+2 or a dreadnoughts close combat weapon 1d3+3</string>
    <string name="skill" >Skill: This is a statistic found on your unit\'s datasheet, listed under the heading WS or BS. This number is expressed as a "X+" with X being a result on a six sided dice. This represents the minimum result required to successfully hit a target with a ranged weapon (Ballistic Skill) or a melee weapon (Weapon Skill)</string>
    <string name="strength">Strength: A weapon or model stat that determines how powerful their attacks are, expressed on the data sheet as “S”, and can be modified based on the weapon used. For example a melee weapon may have “+3” listed as its Strength meaning the weapons total strength is the models base +3 for the weapon</string>
    <string name="toughness" >Toughness: A model\'s durability, expressed on the sheet as “T”</string>
    <string name="wounds">Wounds: The successful hits that are converted into wounds that the enemy must make their armor or invulnerable saves against</string>



</resources>